kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
Byakugan!
Why did you take down Naruto
with her?!
It was an accident...
Had I not applied the finishing blow
to her at the moment,
we would've been in danger instead.
I know of no instance
of the Ninja Art: Kujaku
being defeated up until now...
He will be missed.
Hidden Leaf Shinobi,
your mission is over.
I still haven't taken back the star.
We'll search for it by ourselves.
Thank you for your help.
The Truth About Why
the Hoshikage Was Silenced
Rest easy... I'm not an enemy.
Come to think of it...
What happened after I fell off the cliff?
Could it be...?
Did you save me, lady?
Yes...
I see.
I don't really remember, though...
Well anyway, you saved me! Thanks.
I'm Naruto, a ninja from
the Village Hidden in the Leaves and...
I came to protect the star, but...
You kind of stole it, lady.
I'm Natsuhi...
Natsuhi? What?
I've heard that name before...
That red star's sure pretty.
Natsuhiboshi...
It watches over me all the time.
It's the same name
as Natsuhiboshi.
If I remember right,
Sumaru said it's a star
that protects him!
Sumaru said that?
Yeah! Say, lady,
do you know him?
Sumaru is my child.
What?! So, you're Sumaru's mom?!
What?! Sumaru escaped?!
I am very sorry.
I was careless thinking
the muscle relaxants were still in effect.
Most likely the guys from
the Hidden Leaf
are the ones who took him away...
What do we do?
It'd be bad news if these circumstances
were to be known
by the Leaf. No,
by those in our village.
We've got to look high and low
for Sumaru right away.
There's no need to get rattled...
We can take care of them at
our leisure after we find the star.
I got it. If we tell the Village Hidden
in the Leaves something like
they died during the mission...
We could also convince Sumaru.
I burned Natsuhi's chakra
into my memory.
We'll reach the star
if we follow the remnants
of her chakra.
Naruto was...?
Yeah. Along with the Kunoichi
who stole the star.
But I didn't see them
in the Valley of Death...
Are you saying they escaped from
the valley
where the poison gas swirls?
Perhaps.
If that's the case,
they might have crossed the border
and escaped safely to the forest...
Hey, let's all look for them!
What's the deal, guys?!
Naruto helped all of you,
didn't he?!
But if we don't have an order
from Lord Akahoshi... Right?
Yeah...
We don't have time to be waiting
for an order! I'm going!
I'm going...
I'll go too, if it's to look for Naruto.
Mizura, you can't.
I want to be useful in some way.
No... I'll go.
Sumaru?!
You're okay!
We safely rescued him from
the Hoshikage's medical room
where he was being held!
What? Why was he in
Lord Hoshikage's medical room?
It wasn't a ninja from
some other village
who knocked you all out
and took Sumaru away!
Akahoshi, the leader of your village
was the culprit!
In other words, the Shinobi
who made off with the star
and the Shinobi who attacked all
of you were different people.
That's what Neji deduced
word for word.
Why would Lord Akahoshi...?
Why would he do that to us?
What does this mean, Sumaru?
I don't know, either!
But it seems Lord Akahoshi
is hiding something from us.
Isn't it about time you guys realized it?
Akahoshi's using you as he pleases.
Mizura is not the exception.
If you guys continue
training this way,
everyone will collapse and then...
No way...
It can't be. That's a lie!
Lord Akahoshi is not that
kind of person, ever!
Perhaps the Shinobi
who stole the star will tell the truth.
Let's find the Shinobi who disappeared,
whatever the cost!
The forest in the Land of Bears
is deep.
If only outsiders go,
they'd just get lost.
Okay, work with us.
So leave this to me.
But...
You rest now.
At some point, the time will come
when we'll need your help.
How about it, Akahoshi...?
Were you able to get a lead on
the remnants of Natsuhi's chakra?
This is good.
I guess this is what's called
good old home cooking.
There's more.
One more bowl!
But why'd you do something like
steal the star, Sumaru's mom?
This is not the first and only time
I took that away.
Ten years ago as well...
Training utilizing that star was painful
for many Shinobi at the time
and even caused many deaths.
My husband Hotarubi and I
who survived the training
thought to seal the star
to prevent any more victims
due to the training.
A tracking unit immediately caught up
with us after we had stolen the star.
Hold it!
Lord Third Hoshikage...
Hotarubi, Natsuhi...
Your thoughts are reasonable...
As it happens, I was also wavering.
But in the position of Hoshikage,
it was difficult to make a decision.
I promise to terminate
the star training.
But the hard-line faction
of the Star Village
might at some point
resume the training...
You two must leave this village!
I want you to keep an eye on
the village from the outside.
And if it seems that the training
will begin once again...
Please stop it with your power.
Lord Hoshikage...
For Sumaru.
Tell Sumaru that... we died.
Please be good to him.
Yes, I understand.
Upon allowing us to leave the village,
the Lord Third Hoshikage completely
prohibited the star training.
Like us, the Third Hoshikage
was also distressed
at the damage from
the star training.
Neji was also talking about that.
But are the effects from
the star that severe?!
Yes. My husband Hotarubi died
due to side effects
a while after leaving the village...
I might also die at any time
from the effects.
No way...
Then let's go back to
the village!
Tell Akahoshi directly to
stop the training!
Akahoshi is a man who puts
the prosperity of the village
ahead of the lives of
the children.
As proof of that,
he has taken Sumaru hostage
and has demanded that
I return the star.
What?! Then the masked ninja
from that time was...
Hold it!
Farewell!
What?!
It was Akahoshi?!
What is it, Sumaru's mom?